{"data":[{"question":"Mexico changed from a country with a wheat ________ to one that was a wheat exporter.","a":"lack","b":"length","c":"shortage","d":"inadequacy","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Shortage: a situation in which there is not enough of something that people need= lack of.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Charlie Chaplin was not an instant ________ in Hollywood.","a":"succeed","b":"successful","c":"success","d":"unsuccessful","answer":"3","explain":"\n+ Noun phrase: (a\/an\/the )Adj + Noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"I got a very ________ welcome when I finally arrived.","a":"enthusiastic","b":"enthusiasm","c":"enthusiastically","d":"enthusiast","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Noun phrase: (a\/an\/the ) + (Very) Adj + Noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm looking for a ________ job.","a":"temporality","b":"temporize","c":"temporary","d":"temporal","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Noun phrase: (a\/an\/the ) + (Very) Adj + Noun.\u00a0\n- Temporary: continuing for only a limited period of time.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1829, Morse sailed ________ Europe to study classic art in Italy.","a":"to","b":"for","c":"in","d":"at","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sail to somewhere = to travel somewhere by boat\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Was it Bell who ________ the telephone?","a":"invented","b":"discovered","c":"creased","d":"made","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Invent: to make, design, or think of a new type of thing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"The rulers of Vietnam's last imperial line, the Nguyen Dynasty, all came from ________ family.","a":"same","b":"the same","c":"different","d":"the other","answer":"2","explain":"\n- In fact. all Kings in Nguyen Dynasty are in one family- same.\u00a0\n- Same:used as an adjective(after the and followed by a noun)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"When a body enters the earth's atmosphere, it travels ________.","a":"very rapidly","b":"in a rapid manner","c":"fastly","d":"with great speed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use an adverb after a verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Thank you for bringing me along. I never thought Shakespeare could be so ________ fun.","a":"many","b":"much","c":"few","d":"some","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0\n- We use so with \"much,many, few, a few, little..\") not with \"some, any\".","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"You should say ________ and do ________.","a":"many \/ few","b":"much \/ little","c":"few \/ many","d":"little \/ much","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use little and much as adverbs after say and do","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"}]}